Yes, I Do is a romance, tv movie film directed by Christie Will Wolf.
Busy chocolatier Charlotte has left her boyfriend James at the altar three times and
now she needs to prove to him that she really does want to marry him.
Things are complicated when James’ ex-girlfriend Nicole, who is also the owner of
Chocolate Monthly Magazine, arrives on the scene and says she wants him back.
Charlotte Bennet, played by Jen Lilley.
James Copper, played by Marcus Rosner.
Nicole Sweeney, played by Jessica Lowndes.
Hannah, played by Christie Laing.
Madeline, played by Rhonda Dent.
Jim Reporting, played by Mark Brandon.
Yes Day is a 2021 American family comedy film directed by Miguel Arteta, from a screenplay and screen story by Justin
Malen, based upon the children's book of the same name by Amy Krouse Rosenthal and Tom Lichtenheld.
It stars Jennifer Garner, Édgar Ramírez, and Jenna Ortega.
The movie was released on March 12, 2021 on Netflix.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the acting
(particularly that of Ortega) but criticized its writing and humor.
At the 2021 Imagen Awards, Ortega was nominated
for Best Actress in a Feature Film.
A sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of ex-girlfriend, chocolaterie,
business woman, canceled wedding, wedding plans.
The tone is emotional.